세상에, 내 동생이
결혼을 하다니
I can't believe
my little brother's married!
그러게!
사랑의 도피를 했다 이거지?
Why didn't you tell me
you were eloping?
그렇게 됐어
법원에서 점심을 먹다가...
Well, we were at court,
eating lunch
잠깐, 법원엔 왜 갔어?
Why were you at the courthouse?
We were having lunch.
점심 먹으러
We were like...
법원에서 점심 먹다가
그냥 결혼해버렸지
...we're here, we're having lunch.
Let's get married! Right?
작년에는 동생도 없었는데
이제 올케까지 생겼네
A year ago, I didn't know I had
a brother. Now I have a sister!
Oh, it's so great.
정말 잘됐다
Okay.
그래
됐어
Stop it! Don't!
집어치워
I'll get you a gift now.
선물을 하고 싶은데
뭐 필요한 거 있어?
Is there anything you need?
그래
We've been trying to get pregnant since
we got engaged, to get a jump on things.
아이를 가지려고 했어요
약혼한 뒤로 좀 서둘렀죠
No one's getting any younger.
한 살이라도 젊었을 때
Because the thing is, we're not
able to, you know, conceive.
근데 임신이 불가능하대
We've seen a bunch of doctors.
의사도 많이 만나봤어요
They say that our only chance
to have a baby...
아이를 가지는 유일한 방법은
...is that if they take my sperm,
her egg, put it together in a dish...
내 정자와 이 사람 난자를
접시에서 섞어
...and put it into another girl.
다른 여자한테 넣는 건데
누나한테 부탁 좀 하려고
We were wondering
if you could be that girl.
That's a really nice gift.
멋진 선물이 되겠다
난 육수 그릇을 생각했는데
I was thinking of a gravy boat.
We know it's a lot to ask.
무리한 부탁인 줄은 알지만
We don't have anyone else to go to.
We could pay someone...
달리 알아볼 데도 없고
다른 사람 구할 돈도 없어요
...but we don't have
that kind of money.
Plus, you know, you're
family and, you know...
게다가 누나는 가족이잖아
...I just don't want my baby to grow into
some chick I don't know, you know?
출신도 모르는 여자를
생모로 만들 순 없잖아
Don't give us an answer yet,
think about it.
천천히 생각해보세요
And if you say no,
we'll totally understand.
거절해도 충분히 이해해요
Okay. Okay.
네, 알았어요
And we were wondering if you could
give us a ride down to the train station.
그리고 기차역에
데려다 줬으면 하는데
Well, actually, we kind of need
an answer to that one right now.
그 대답은 지금 해줘야겠어
The One with Phoebe's Uterus
얘들아, 이걸 봐
내가 어디 취직했게?
Check it out!
Guess what job I just got.
I don't know, but Donald Trump
wants his blue blazer black.
어찌 됐건 도널드 트럼프가
청색 블레이저 돌이켜 달래
What?
뭐?
Blue blazer back.
He wants it back.
청색 블레이저 돌려 달라고
You said "black." Why would he
want his blue blazer black?
돌이켜 달라니, 왜 청색
블레이저를 돌이켜?
Well, you know what I meant.
알면서 왜 이래
You messed it up.
너 말 꼬였다
You're stupid.
이런 멍청이!
So, what job did you get?
무슨 일을 맡았는데?
Tour guide at the museum.
Ross got it for me.
박물관 투어가이드야
로스가 소개했지
공룡전문가도 아닌데
어떻게 가이드를 해?
Don't you have to be
a dinosaur expert?
They give you
all the information.
그건 박물관에서 알려줘
대본 외우는 거나 같아
It's like memorizing a script.
왼쪽은 쥐라기의 육식공룡
티라노사우루스 렉스입니다
On your left you have a tyrannosaurus rex,
from the Jurassic Period.
우와, 멋지다
Very nice.
Yeah, actually, Joey,
it's the Cretaceous Period.
정확히 말하면 백악기야
But I can pronounce Jurassic.
쥐라기 발음이 더 쉽잖아
놀라지 마, 프랭크 주니어와
앨리스가 결혼했어
Frank Jr. and Alice got married!
세상에!
Oh, my God!
그리고 아이를 가질 거래
They're having a baby!
덧붙여 그 아이는
내 뱃속에서 자랄 거래
They want me to grow it
for them in my uterus!
-My God!
-Are you serious?
맙소사
정말이야?
그래
진짜 동생이랑 잘 거야?
You're thinking of
having sex with your brother?
으휴! 아냐!
Ew! And, oh, no!
They want me to be the surrogate.
난 그냥 대리모야, 정자 난자를
제공받는 오븐, 빵은 그쪽 거고
It's her egg and his sperm.
I'm the oven. It's their bun.
What did you say?
넌 뭐랬는데
올케는 천천히 생각하랬지만
I had to think about it first,
but what is there to think of?
생각할 게 뭐 있어
최고의 선물이 될 텐데
I'll be giving someone
the greatest gift.
아이도 낳아주고 소니
플레이스테이션도 사주게?
You'll carry their child
and get them a Sony PlayStation?
물론 좋은 일이긴 하지만
그렇게 간단한 게 아냐
This is an incredible thing to do.
But there are things to think about.
임신을 하는 거야
임신이 된다고
Yeah, you'd be pregnant.
I mean, pregnant.
알아
I know.
많은 고통을 겪게 돼
입덧에다 분만까지
You'll put your body
through an awful lot.
I mean, morning sickness, labor.
It's all for somebody else.
본인 일도 아닌데
Yeah. What's your point?
그래, 요점이 뭐야?
방금 그게 요점인데
Well, the stuff I just mentioned.
나라면 상상도 못해
내가 첫아이를 갖는다면
I couldn't do that.
I always figured the first time I had a baby,
it'd be with someone I love.
그 아이는 엄마와 아빠의
사랑을 지켜주는 파수꾼이거든
And that baby was, you know...
...a keeper.
너희들 내가 데님 가구 만든다고
했을 때도 이렇게 나오진 않았어
You were more supportive when
I wanted to make denim furniture.
If you decide to do this,
we'll be supportive like crazy.
일단 네가 결정을 내리면
우린 모두 네 편이야
그래
Just think it through.
신중히 생각해
Talk to somebody who's had a baby.
Like your mom.
경험 있는 사람하고
얘기해보든지, 너희 엄마
My mom never gave birth.
Oh! But my birth mom did!
엄마는 애 낳은 적 없어
오! 우리 생모가 계셨구나
이 엉덩이 너무 좋아
I love this tushy!
Can I take it to work with me?
직장에 가져가도 돼?
어차피 내 것도 아냐
바지 살 때 묻어왔거든
Yeah, sure. It's not mine anyway.
It came with the pants.
I am so jealous.
너무 질투 난다
You guys are just right there.
바로 그 단계구나
Yes.
그래
Right where?
그 단계라니
처음엔 섹스와 대화
섹스와 대화...
The beginning, where
it's all sex and talking...
...and sex and talking.
You got to love the talking.
그래, 대화 좋지
-And the sex?
-We haven't had sex.
- 그리고 섹스는?
- 아직 섹스는 없었어
What's the big deal?
This is special.
무슨 상관이야, 다음 단계로
가려면 사랑이 무르익어야지
I want our love to grow
before moving to the next level.
너무 멋지다
Oh, Chandler, that is so nice.
그래, 멋진... 뻥이지
That is really nice...
...Iying!
다른 이유가 있어
-No way is that the reason.
-Why?
왜? 넌 철이 없어서
이해를 못할 뿐이겠지
Because you're not mature enough
to understand that?
He's right. I'm totally lying.
맞아, 완전 뻥이야
Then what is it?
이유가 뭔데
캐시는 조이의 애인이었어
Kathy's last boyfriend was Joey.
And you're afraid you won't
be able to fill his shoes?
녀석의 공간을 채우기가
부담스럽다는 거겠지?
I'm afraid I won't
make love as well as him.
아니, 조이만큼
잘할 자신이 없어
-I was going for the metaphor.
-I was saying the actual words.
난 돌려서 말한 거야
난 톡 까놓고 말했어
He's had a lot of girlfriends.
Doesn't mean he's great in bed.
바람둥이라고 꼭 테크닉이
훌륭하다는 보장은 없잖아
We share a wall.
벽 하나 사이였어
조이가 잘했든지
캐시가 박자를 잘 맞췄나 봐
Either he's great, or she liked
to agree with him a lot.
Loudly and a lot.
대단히 소란스럽게!
All night long she'd agree.
밤새 박자를 맞췄어!
넌 다르잖아, 사랑한다면
섹스도 좋을 거야
It'll be different. The sex will be
great because you're in love.
- 정말?
- 그럼
-Just go for it.
-Yeah, you should.
힘내라, 챈들러
잘 된다니까
All right. I'll sleep
with my girlfriend.
좋아, 한번 자볼게
But I'm just doing it for you guys.
너희들을 위해서야
Now, the mastodon is from
the semi-late Jurassic Period.
마스토돈은 쥐라기
중후반에 나타났어요
Isn't the mastodon
from the Pliocene Epoch?
마스토돈은 신생대
제3기 아닌가요?
쉬잇! 박물관에서는
떠드는 거 아냐
This is a museum. No talking.
Right down here we have...
자, 이건...
커다란 발이다
...a large foot.
And over here we have Ross Geller.
이 사람은 로스 겔러
Everyone wave "hi" to Ross.
손을 흔들어주세요
Ross is one of our scientists.
Look at him hard at work.
박물관 최고의 과학자지
일하시는 걸 잘 보거라
Okay, moving right along.
자, 이동합시다... 어서
Come on.
It's open. Come in.
열렸어요, 들어와요
저 왔어요
늦어서 죄송해요
-I'm sorry I'm late.
-That's okay.
괜찮다, 덕분에
젖꼭지에 광도 냈어
I had time to finish
glazing my nipples.
You go all out
when you're expecting company.
손님맞이 준비가 확실하네요
I was working on my pottery.
내 도자기 말이다
Oh! I didn't know
that you did pot.
미처 몰랐어요
옹기씩이나
Mostly nudes. It combines
my two passions: pottery and erotica.
대부분 누드지
두 가지 열정의 융합이야
도자기와 에로티카
Erottery!
에로자기!
저런! 그거 좋구나
Thanks for coming out to see me.
와줘서 고맙다, 아기 문제는
직접 만나 상의하고 싶었어
I thought it'd be a good idea to
talk about this baby stuff in person.
네
I don't think it's a good idea.
좋은 생각이 아닌 것 같다
Why not?
왜죠?
결국 아이를 포기해야 돼
You'd be giving up a baby.
And I really don't
자기 아이를 포기하는 게
어떤 고통인지 모를 거다
I don't know if anything I said...
...would make you understand the pain
of giving up a baby.
그래서...
No, no, I understand the pain.
Don't hurt the puppy!
안 돼요, 그 고통 아니까
강아지 고문하지 마세요
No, no. The puppy is yours.
너한테 주는 거야
-I get a puppy?
-But for only three days.
내 강아지예요?
그래, 하지만 딱 사흘이야
왜요?
Why?
이제 와서 엄마 노릇할
자격은 별로 없겠지만...
I realize I don't have any right
to start getting parent-y on you now.
피비, 나 좀 볼래?
중요한 일이야
Look at me and not the puppy.
It's very important.
알았어요
잘 새겨들어라
I know what I'm talking about.
난 아이 둘을 포기했다
I gave up two babies.
그 고통을 미리 알았더라면
절대 그런 짓은 안 했을 거야
I only wish I had someone
who'd given up babies that told me...
...how terrible it is.
I really shouldn't have
given you the puppy first.
강아지를 먼저 준 게 실수다
That's okay.
No, we're listening.
됐어요, 말씀하세요
It'd be something you'd regret
every day for the rest of your life.
평생을 후회하며 살게 될 거야
So however hard it is for you
to give up this puppy...
강아지를 포기하는 것도
힘들겠지만
...it'd be a million times harder
to give up a child.
자기 자식을 포기하는 건
그보다 수천 배 더 힘들어
Okay, fair enough. Three days.
네, 좋아요
사흘
Oh, it's time to take
my ass out of the kiln.
그만 엉덩이 떼라는구나
Could you sit there? I'm saving
this seat for my friend Ross.
저쪽에 앉으실래요?
제 친구 로스 자리라서
You mean Dr. Geller?
닥터 겔러 말인가요?
Doctor? I didn't know
he had a nickname.
닥터? 별명도 있었나?
Oh, he won't sit here.
여기 안 앉으실 텐데
흰색 가운은 저기 앉고
청색 블레이저는 여기예요
Only people in white coats
sit there.
Only people in blue blazers
sit here.
-How come?
-That's just the way it is.
그건 왜죠?
그냥 그래요
That's crazy.
말도 안돼
옷의 차별이 없는 완벽한
세상에선 말이 안되겠지만
Maybe it's crazy in a perfect world:
a world without lab coats and blazers.
But you not in a perfect world.
You in a museum now.
여긴 완벽한 세상이 아니라
박물관이에요
See that scientist?
안경 쓴 과학자 보여요?
초등학교 단짝친구였죠
He and I used to play together
in grade school, but now....
근데 지금은...
Peter! Hey, Peter!
피터!
야, 피터!
It's me! Rhonda, from P.S. 129?
나야, 론다!
129 공립학교!
I shared my pudding with you, man!
나랑 푸딩 나눠먹었지?
까까봉지도 줬잖아!
I gave you my Snack Pack!
See? He pretend
he don't even hear me!
봤죠? 못 들은 척하는 거!
여기 사람들은 다
못 들은 척 하네요
Everyone's pretending
they don't hear you.
I don't know about your jackets
and separate tables...
보세요, 옷이야 어찌 됐건
우린 둘도 없는 친구입니다
...but Ross is my friend.
And if I save him a seat,
he will sit in it.
내가 자리를 맡았으면
꼭 여기 앉을 거예요
로스! 로스!
Here! I saved you a seat!
내가 자리 맡아놨어
I'm cool here.
I'll catch up with you later.
난 여기서 먹을게
나중에 보자
임자 있어요
This is saved.
Gift shop.
매점직원용
저기, 오늘 일은
정말 미안하다
I'm really, really sorry about what
happened in the cafeteria today.
You do what you got to do.
괜찮아, 방침이
그렇다는데 뭐
The scientists and the tour guides
never sit together.
내 잘못이 아니라 과학자와
투어가이드는 합석을 안 해
Whatever.
어련하겠어
It's like that everywhere.
Mon, back me up.
어디든 마찬가지야, 조이
모니카, 너도 직장에서...
Where you work, the waiters
eat with the waiters.
웨이터는 웨이터끼리
요리사는 요리사끼리 먹지?
And the chefs eat
with the other chefs?
I eat by myself in the alley,
because everybody hates me.
난 골목에서 혼자 먹어
나 거기서 왕따잖아
Okay, Rach, when was the last time
you had lunch with the shipping clerks?
레이첼, 넌 잡역부하고
점심 먹은 적 있어?
I've never had lunch
with the shipping clerks...
먹은 적 없지만 우린 상황이
좀 달라, 간부전용식당이거든
...but it's totally different. They're not
allowed in the executive cafeteria.
Oh, I see what you're saying.
무슨 말인지 알겠다
Look, Ross.
야, 로스
It's no big deal.
정말 괜찮아, 넌 흰색 가운
난 푸른색 블레이저
You wear a white coat.
I wear a blue blazer.
If that means we can't be
friends at work, so be it.
꼭 직장에서 우정을
확인할 필요는 없으니까
I understand, you know?
나도 연기 중에 객석에 있는
너희들과 얘기 못하잖아
When I'm in a play and you're in
the audience, I don't talk to you.
So it's, you know, it's cool.
신경 쓰지 마
내일 보자
I'll see you tomorrow.
얘기는 안 했지만
손을 흔들었잖아
When we're in the audience,
he doesn't talk but he does wave.
Who's my puppy? Who's my puppy?
Who's my puppy?
내 새끼, 내 새끼
귀여운 내 새끼
-Have you named him yet?
-No, I don't want to get attached.
이름 지었니?
정 붙이기 싫어
-Can I hold him?
-Sure. Here.
- 안아봐도 돼?
- 그래
이리 온
-Come here, squirmy. Hello
-Not like that. No.
- 안녕?
- 그렇게 하면 안돼!
나야
Why's Phoebe singing
to Karl Malden?
칼 말든이 여긴 웬일이지?
I think it's time for puppy
to go out again.
또 마려운 모양이다
자, 발코니로 나가자
Come on, let's go to the balcony.
뭐?
The street.
Come on, let's go to the street.
어? 밖에
밖으로 가자
내가 올 때까지
발코니에 나가지 마
Don't go on the balcony
until after I get back.
So did you do it?
어때, 했어?
Yes, yes, we had the sex.
그래, 저질렀다
It was bad?
별로였니?
It was fine, but she didn't agree
with me as strongly as with Joey.
괜찮았지만 조이하고 했듯이
찐하게 박자를 맞추진 않더라
그래도 엇박자로
안 나간 게 어디야
She was like, "l see your point.
I'm all right with it."
There's not always a lot of agreement
the first time.
처음부터 완벽하게
맞을 순 없잖아
Yeah. Not for girls, anyway.
Guys agree like that.
그래, 여자들은 아니지
남자들은 이걸로 끝나
Look, you have to help me.
얘들아, 나 좀 도와줘
I mean....
I know what to do with a woman.
It's always nice.
나도 웬만한 건 알아
뭐 그런 대로 괜찮지만
I need to know...
난 이런 말이 듣고 싶어
'저 여자 죽는 거 아냐?'
...what makes it go from nice to:
"My God! Somebody's killing her
in there!"
I'll show you something
a lot of guys don't know.
좋아, 한 수 가르쳐주지
그것 좀 줘봐
All right.
그래... 보자
Now.
You don't have to draw an actual
Whoa, she's hot!
굳이 그림까지...
워! 빠방한데?
Everyone knows the erogenous zones.
이건 기본적인 성감대
1번, 2번, 3번...
You got one, two, three...
...four...
4번
5번, 6번...
그리고 7번
...five, six and seven.
There are seven?
7번씩이나?
Let me see that.
어디 보자
Oh, yeah.
그래, 좋다
That's one?
여기도?
Kind of an important one.
중요한 데야
I was looking at it upside down.
거꾸로 보고 있었구나
Well, you know, sometimes that helps.
때론 그것도 효과가 있지
남자들은 대개 1, 2, 3에서
7로 가서 파장을 내버리거든
Most guys will hit one, two, three
and then go to seven and set up camp.
그건 안 좋아?
That's bad?
디즈니랜드에 가서
종일 롤러코스터만 탈래?
At Disneyland, you don't spend
the whole day on the Matterhorn.
You might if it were like seven.
그게 7번이라면
All right, the important thing
is to take your time.
서두르지 않는 게 관건이야
You want to hit them all...
각개격파와 혼합전술
발가락 끝까지
...mix them up.
Keep them on their toes.
Oh, toes!
오, 발가락!
누군 거기가 좋대
For some people.
좋아
All right.
You could start out
with a little one.
1번부터 가볍게
시작해서... 2번
A two.
A one, two, three.
1, 2, 3
A three.
A five.
5...
A four.
A three, two.
3, 2
Two. A two, four, six.
2, 4, 6
Two, four, six.
Four. Two.
Two. Four, seven!
4, 7
Five, seven! Six, seven!
5, 7
6, 7
Seven! Seven!
7! 7!
Seven! Seven! Seven! Seven!
Seven! Seven!
7! 7! 7!
7! 7! 7! 7!
Seven!
And there you are.
그거야
Yeah, that'll work.
그럼 잘 될 거야
Dr. Geller?
There's a seat here.
닥터 겔러, 여기 앉아요
Thank you, Dr. Phillips.
대단히 고맙습니다만 저는
이 중간 식탁을 택하렵니다
But I'm having my lunch...
...at this table.
Here in the middle.
I'm having my lunch...
점심은 제 친구 조이와
함께 여기서 먹겠어요
...right here
with my good friend, Joey.
If he'll sit with me.
합석해준다면
I will sit with you, Dr. Geller.
합석하렵니다, 박사님
아시다시피 여기는
자연사 박물관입니다
You know...
...we work in a museum
of natural history.
And yet, there is something...
하지만 우리가 점심을 먹는
모습은 자연스럽지가 못합니다
...unnatural...
...about the way we eat lunch.
한 투어가이드가 이 과학자의
실수를 깨닫게 했습니다
Now, I want you to know...
...it took a tour guide to show
this scientist the error of his ways.
You might even say he took
me on a tour...
제 내면의 투어를
독려했던 것이지요
...of myself.
Yeah, that was me.
네, 접니다
이 식당을 둘러보면
장벽이 느껴집니다
I look around, and you know what I see?
I see division.
Division between people in white coats
and people in blue blazers.
흰색 가운과 청색 블레이저
사이의 장벽, 왜들 이러십니까!
I ask myself, "My God, why?"
Now, I say we shed these coats...
우리 사이를 갈라놓는
이 허울을 벗어버리고
...that separate us.
And we get to know
the people underneath.
내면의 모습을 바라봅시다
I'm Ross!
전 로스입니다!
애 딸린 이혼남이죠!
I'm divorced and I have a kid!
I'm Joey! I'm an actor!
조이라고 합니다, 배우죠
공룡이라곤 쥐뿔도 몰라요
I don't know squat about dinosaurs!
I'm Ted, and I just moved here,
and New York really scares me.
한 달 전에 이사 온 테드인데
뉴욕은 진짜 살 떨리는 동네군요
- 아주 좋습니다!
- 그렇게만 합시다
-There you go!
-Hang in there, Teddy!
I'm Andrew.
난 앤드류요
이 배를 훔쳤소
And I didn't pay for this pear.
Okay. Good for you.
네, 좋아요
I'm Rhonda!
And these aren't real!
난 론다!
이건 가짜예요!
Wow, Rhonda.
와우, 론다...
-I'm Scott.
-Yeah, okay, Scott!
- 난 스캇!
- 좋아요, 스캇!
I flip the light switch on and off
17 times when I leave a room...
외출할 땐 전기스위치를 17번씩
껐다 켰다 해야 가족이 무사해요
...or my family will die.
My mom's gonna be here any minute.
엄마가 곧 올 텐데
이 녀석을 어떻게 포기하지?
I can't. I can't give him up.
아냐, 할 수 있어
Yes, no. I can.
I don't want to.
돌려주기 싫어
But I can.
그래도 할 수 있어
No.
아니
I can't watch this.
It's like Sophie's Choice.
'소피의 선택' 같아
더는 못 보겠다
You know, I never saw that.
난 그 영화 못 봤어
Oh, it was only okay.
별거 없더라
I can't do this.
난 못해
My mom was right.
If I can't give him up...
엄마가 맞았어
얘도 포기 못하는데
...there's no way
I can give up a baby.
아기를 어떻게 포기해
동생네 부부가
크게 실망할 텐데
Frank and Alice
are going to be so crushed.
What else can I give them?
A kidney!
다른 걸 주면 어떨까, 콩팥?
- 저희 왔어요
- 어서 와요
We were in the neighborhood.
우연히 근처에 왔다가...
We want to let you know that
there's still no pressure.
혹시나 해서 들렀어
부담 갖지 말라고
할말 있으면 부르셔도 돼요
저쪽에서 커피 마실 테니까
If there was something you wanted
to say, we'll be right there.
알았어요
이 녀석은 뭐야?
Who's this little guy?
귀엽다, 전에 키우던
쭈글이랑 비슷해
He's so cute! He reminds me
of my old dog, Tumor.
You are so precious,
I could take you home.
너 우리랑 같이 살래?
Why don't you?
데려가요
-Are you serious?
-Yeah.
진짜야?
그럼
Thanks.
고마워
-What are you doing?
-I'm okay with this.
뭐 하는 거야
난 괜찮아
왠지 알아?
You know why?
Because look at them.
저렇게들 좋아하잖아
Look how happy they are.
내가 행복을 선사한 거야
And I made that, so you know....
It'll be a million times harder
to give up a baby, but oh, my God!
아기를 포기하는 건
이보다 훨씬 힘들겠지만
It'll feel a million times
better, right?
그만큼 더 뿌듯하지 않겠어?
I'll do this.
I want to carry your baby.
할 거야, 아기를 낳을게요
Thank you so much!
정말 고마워요
You don't know what this means to us.
무슨 말을 해야 할지
I think I'm going to cry!
나 눈물 쏟아진다
It's going to be so great.
잘 될 거야
얘들아, 무슨 일이니
-What's going on?
-I gave them the puppy.
강아지를 주니까 너무 좋아해서
아이를 낳기로 했어요
It made them so happy,
I decided to carry their baby.
-Phoebe
-No, I know.
- 피비...
- 아니에요
엄마랑 난 달라요
상황도 전혀 다르구요
We're different, though.
This is a different situation.
I am not going to regret this.
후회하지 않을 거예요
I understand all that.
그건 이해한다만...
It's just, that was my puppy.
저건 내 개야
Would you ever be a surrogate?
넌 대리모 될 수 있어?
Depends who asked.
누구 부탁이냐에 달렸지
What if I asked?
내 부탁이라면?
Oh, Mon, sure!
모니카, 물론이지
-Really?
-Yes.
- 정말?
- 그럼
You're not asking me, are you?
진짜 부탁할 거야?
-No.
-Yes. Totally.
- 아니
- 당연히 해줘야지
Thank you! Thank you!
고마워요! 고마워요!
Thank you!
Yes, thank you!
고마워요
정말 고마워요!